Guide to the Olga Rudge Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Rudge-Pound Correspondence, 1923-69; Series I; 15.75; (32 boxes)
  - Correspondence, 1950 Dec (Box 27, Folder 769-71)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Jan (Box 27, Folder 772-73)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Feb (Box 27, Folder 774-75)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Mar (Box 27, Folder 776-77)
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 778-79)
  - Correspondence, 1951 May (Box 27, Folder 780-82)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Jun (Box 28, Folder 783-85)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Jul (Box 28, Folder 786-87)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Aug (Box 28, Folder 788-89)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Sep (Box 28, Folder 790)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Oct (Box 28, Folder 791-92)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Nov (Box 28, Folder 793-95)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Dec (Box 28, Folder 796-97)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Jan (Box 28, Folder 798-99)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Feb (Box 28, Folder 800-01)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Mar (Box 28, Folder 802-03)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Apr (Box 28, Folder 804)
  - Correspondence, 1952 May (Box 28, Folder 805-06)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Jun (Box 28, Folder 807)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Jul (Box 28, Folder 808-09)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Aug (Box 28, Folder 810)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Sep (Box 28, Folder 811)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Oct (Box 28, Folder 812-13)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Nov (Box 29, Folder 814)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 815-16)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Jan (Box 29, Folder 817-18)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Feb (Box 29, Folder 819-20)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Mar (Box 29, Folder 821-22)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Apr (Box 29, Folder 823)
  - Correspondence, 1953 May (Box 29, Folder 824-25)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Jun (Box 29, Folder 826-27)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Jul (Box 29, Folder 828)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Aug (Box 29, Folder 829)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Sep (Box 29, Folder 830-31)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Oct (Box 29, Folder 832)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Nov (Box 29, Folder 833)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Dec (Box 29, Folder 834)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Jan (Box 29, Folder 835-36)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Feb (Box 29, Folder 837-38)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Mar (Box 29, Folder 839-40)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Apr (Box 29, Folder 841)
  - Correspondence, 1954 May (Box 29, Folder 842)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Jun (Box 29, Folder 843)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Jul (Box 29, Folder 844)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Aug (Box 30, Folder 845)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Sep (Box 30, Folder 846)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Oct (Box 30, Folder 847-48)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Nov (Box 30, Folder 849)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Dec (Box 30, Folder 850-51)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Jan (Box 30, Folder 852)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Feb (Box 30, Folder 853)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Mar (Box 30, Folder 854-55)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Apr (Box 30, Folder 856)
  - Correspondence, 1955 May (Box 30, Folder 857)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Jun (Box 30, Folder 858)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Jul (Box 30, Folder 859)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 860)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 861)
  - Correspondence, [1946-58?] (Box 30, Folder 862)
  - Correspondence, 1959 Jan-Feb (Box 30, Folder 863)
  - Correspondence, 1959 Mar-Apr (Box 30, Folder 864)
  - Correspondence, 1959 Jun (Box 30, Folder 865)
  - Correspondence, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 30, Folder 866)
  - Correspondence, [1959] (Box 30, Folder 867)
  - Correspondence, 1960 Feb-Dec (Box 30, Folder 868)
  - Correspondence, 1961 Jan-Jul (Box 30, Folder 869)
  - Correspondence, 1961 Aug-Oct (Box 30, Folder 870)
  - Correspondence, 1961 Nov-Dec (Box 30, Folder 871)
  - Correspondence, 1962 Jan-Mar (Box 30, Folder 872)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 873)
  - Correspondence, [1962?] (Box 30, Folder 874)
  - Correspondence, 1965 Feb (Box 30, Folder 875)
  - Correspondence, [1960s] (Box 30, Folder 876)
  - Empty envelopes, 1923-59 (Box 31, Folder 877-85)
  - Empty envelopes, 1960-69, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 886-92)
- General Correspondence, 1904-89; Series II; 29.5; (60 boxes)
  Series II, General Correspondence, is housed in Boxes 33-92 and contains alphabetically arranged correspondence. All letters have been placed in chronological order within each listing, with undated letters at the end; individuals have been listed separately whenever there are four or more items to or from that person. Third-party correspondence, unidentified letters, and empty envelopes are located at the end of the series.
  - "A" general, 1938-87, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 893-95)
  - Abbott, Beatrice, 1947-48 (Box 33, Folder 896)
  - Academy of American Poets, 1972, 1973
  - Accademia Musicale Chigiana, 1947-63, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 897)
    See also: Luciano Alberti, Box 33, folder 901
    See also: Guido Chigi-Saracini, Box 40, folder 1079
    See also: Armando Vannini, Box 81, folder 2176
  - Adam: International Review
    See: Miron Grindea, Box 49, folder 1326
  - Adler, Herman, 1952 Dec 31 (Box 33, Folder 898)
  - Adriana, Margaret, 1960-61 (Box 33, Folder 899)
  - Agresti, Olivia Rossetti, 1948-58, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 900)
  - Agenda
    See: William Cookson, Box 42, folder 1124
  - Ajou, Guido, 1955, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 901)
  - Alberti, Luciano, 1970-89
  - Aldrich, Chester, 1940, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 902)
  - Alexander, Michael, 1962-79 (Box 33, Folder 903)
  - Alfani Tellini, Inés, 1950-60, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 904-06)
  - Alistair, 1932, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 907)
  - Alldritt, Keith, 1981, 1982
  - Allen, Robert, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 908)
  - Alvarez, José Maria, 1984-85 (Box 33, Folder 909)
  - Ambrosini, Pietro, 1963-82, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 910-11)
  - Amyot, Etienne, 1955-71, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 912)
  - Anderson, David, 1980-81 (Box 33, Folder 913)
  - Antheil, Boski, 1936-72, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 914)
  - Antheil, George, 1923-27, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 915-16)
    See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3699
  - Antoninus, Brother
    See: William Everson, Box 46, folder 1244
  - Appia, Edmund, 1955, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 917)
  - Armstrong, George, 1985 Dec 5 (Box 33, Folder 918)
  - Arnold, Kenneth, 1977 Oct 18
  - Arnott, Anne, 1970 Dec 8 (Box 33, Folder 919)
  - Artopoulos-Knowles, Lucia, 1976-79, n.d.
  - Asia Society, 1970
  - Associazione Amici della Fenice
    See: Giorgio Manera, Box 57, folder 1545
  - Associazione Italo-Francese di Cultura, 1972-82, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 920)
  - Astruc, Yvonne, 1954-64, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 921-26)
  - Atwood, Margaret, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 927)
  - Awiszus, Sabine, 1967-85, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 928-31)
  - "B" general, 1933-87, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 932-38)
  - Baar, Rev. William H., 1987-89, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 939)
  - Bacca, Mavis, 1953, 1955
  - Bacigalupo, Giuseppe, 1962-80, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 941)
  - Bacigalupo, Massimo, 1959-85, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 942-43)
  - Bacigalupo Natali, Frieda, 1946-82, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 944-52)
  - Baez, Luis, 1962-64 (Box 35, Folder 953)
  - Bagatti, Costanza, 1949 Jan 27 (Box 35, Folder 954)
  - Baglioni, Piero, 1949-54, n.d.
  - Baglioni, Vittorio, 1952-61, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 955)
  - Bairo Puccetti, Gabriella, 1971-81, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 956)
  - Baker, Carlos, 1968 Oct (Box 35, Folder 957)
  - Bardwell, Marie Louise, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 958)
  - Bardwell, William, 1954-73
  - Barfoot, Gabrielle, 1972-89, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 959)
  - Barilli, Bruno, 1949-52, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 960-66)
  - Barilli Pavlovitch, Danitza, 1952-55 (Box 35, Folder 967)
  - Barnard, Mary, 1949-80, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 968)
  - Barney, Natalie, 1946-65, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 969)
  - Bartholomew, Helen, 1954 Sep 22 (Box 35, Folder 970)
  - Basdevant, Marie Louise, 1967-69
  - Batchelor, Henry, n.d.
  - Batten, Betty, 1963-67 (Box 35, Folder 971)
  - Baumgarten, Alice, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 972)
  - Baumgarten, Franklin, 1980, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 973)
  - Baumgarten, Fritz, 1978-89, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 974)
  - Baumgarten, Gretel, 1979-81 (Box 35, Folder 975)
  - Baumgarten, June, 1978-89, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 976)
  - Baumgarten, Margaret, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 977)
  - Baumgarten, Suzanne, 1948-80, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 978-84)
  - Bavier, Antoine de, 1951-81, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 985-89)
  - Baynes, Lou (Mrs. E. H.), 1955-57, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 990)
  - Beauclair, Gotthard de, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 991)
  - Beckwith, Osmond, 1948 May 13 (Box 36, Folder 992)
  - Beerbohm, Elizabeth, 1968 Dec
  - Belgion, Montgomery, 1953-72
  - Beltrami, Teresa, 1951-81, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 993-94)
  - Benacchio, Margherita, 1952-67 (Box 36, Folder 995)
  - Benson, Lindy
    See: Lindy Melton, Box 57, folder 1566
  - Bennett, Peter, 1986, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 996)
  - Berenson, Mary, 1927 Mar 15
  - Bernheimer, Ilse, 1964-77, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 997)
  - Berri, Dr. Pietro, 1949-72 (Box 36, Folder 998)
  - Bevénot, Lawrence, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 999)
  - Bienek, Horst, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1000)
  - Binyon, A.H., 1921 Dec 12
  - Bisogni, Piero, 1962-65 (Box 36, Folder 1001)
  - Blackburn, Paul, 1951-68, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1002)
  - Blanchard, Winifred (Mrs. Henry), 1952-75, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1003-05)
  - Blazek, Doris
    See: Covington and Burling, Box 42, folder 1133
  - Blom, Eric, 1936-48 (Box 37, Folder 1006)
  - Bolzoni, Roberto, 1983-85 (Box 37, Folder 1007)
  - Bonfante, Jordan, 1963-64 (Box 37, Folder 1008)
  - Borgatti, Renata, 1920-62, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1009-16)
  - Bose, Buddhadeva, 1949 Sep 8 (Box 37, Folder 1017)
  - Boskoff, Georges, 1923-32
  - Boulanger, Nadia, 1924-64, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1018)
  - Bowen, Stella, 1937-46, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1019)
  - Bowness, Alan
    See: Tate Gallery, Box 80, folder 2157
  - Boyle, Kay, 1936 Feb 5
  - Braddock, Jack, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 1020)
  - Brengola, Riccardo Brengola, Giuliana, 1955-61, n.d.
  - Brewster, Fiona, 1959-85, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1021)
  - Bridson, Geoffrey, 1965-78, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1022)
  - Bridson, Joyce, 1966-80, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1023-24)
  - Brinnin, John Malcolm, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 1025)
  - British Museum, 1939, 1954
  - Britseva, Maria, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1026)
  - Browder, Peggy, 1973, n.d.
  - Brown, Arturo, 1931-59, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1027-35)
  - Brown, Gordon, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 1036)
  - Bruers, Milena, 1951-60 (Box 38, Folder 1037)
  - Brun, Else de
    See: Farrell, Patric
  - Bunting, Basil, 1950-52 (Box 38, Folder 1038)
  - Burrell, Kathleen
    See: Kathleen Dale, Box 43, folder 1148
  - Bury, Mairy, 1965-81, n.d.
  - Bush, George, 1988 Dec 8 (Box 38, Folder 1039)
  - "C" general, 1929-88, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1040-45)
  - C. B. S. Television Network
    See: Louis Freedman, Box 47, folder 1280
  - Cadorin, Guido, 1968-74, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1046-51)
  - Caetani-Grenier, G., 1954-57, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1052)
  - Caico, Lina, 1948 Jul 21 (Box 39, Folder 1053)
  - Cambridge University, 1938, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 1054)
  - Campbell, G., 1929 Jul26
  - Canessa. Umberto, 1956-59
  - Caputi, Giuseppe, 1953-59 (Box 39, Folder 1055)
  - Carnill, Michael, 1969 Dec 6
  - Carpanini, Ferdinando, 1966-87 (Box 39, Folder 1056-63)
  - Carpenter, Humphrey, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 1064)
  - Carroll, Donald J., 1985, n.d.
  - Carton de Wiart, E., comtesse, 1955-57, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1065)
  - Casado, Cheiko Casado, Gasparo, 1961, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1066)
  - Casella, Alfredo, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 1067)
  - Casella, Yvonne, 1938-72, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1068-70)
  - Caselli, Vinny, 1951, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1071)
  - Cassa di Risparmio di Venezia, 1945-46, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1072)
  - Castagna, Armando, 1962-65 (Box 39, Folder 1073)
  - Cavalieri, Alix Krasnokoutsky, 1945-53, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1074)
  - Cecchini, Giovanni, 1950-63, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1075)
  - Chase, William, 1975-76 (Box 40, Folder 1076)
  - Chailley-Bert, Jeanne, 1961, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1077)
  - Chambrillon, Paul, n.d.
  - Chauvin, Claire, 1931-36, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1078)
  - Chigi Saracini, Guido, conte, 1933-65, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1079-96)
  - Chiovenda Petrucci, Anna, 1951-73, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1097-1100)
  - Chodorov, Stephan, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1101)
  - Christou, John, 1954-63, n.d.
  - Chute, Desmond, 1933-58, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1102-06)
  - Cini, Walter, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1107)
  - Cipriani family, 1960-80, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1108)
  - Clarke, Ashley, Sir, 1957-87 (Box 41, Folder 1109)
  - Clarke, Lawrence, 1932 Aug 2 (Box 41, Folder 1110)
  - Clerici, Leonardo, 1976-87 (Box 41, Folder 1111)
  - Cobbett, W. W., 1934-36 (Box 41, Folder 1112)
  - Cogni, Giulio, 1950-72 (Box 41, Folder 1113)
  - Coleman, Randolph, 1987 Nov 19
  - Comitato d'Azione Maltese, 1943 May 12 (Box 41, Folder 1114)
  - Comitato per il centenario di Ezra Pound
    See: Antonio Pantano, Box 60, folder 1632
  - Confederazione Fascista dei Professionisti e degli Artisti, 1936-41 (Box 41, Folder 1115)
  - Connolly, Cyril, 1967-73, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1116-18)
  - Contino, Vittorugo, 1967-87, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1119-22)
  - Cookson, Rachel, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1123)
  - Cookson, William, 1970-87, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1124-27)
  - Cooley, Christopher Cooley, Mary, 1971-85, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1128)
  - Cornell, Julian, 1946-65 (Box 42, Folder 1129-30)
  - Cortot, Alfred, 1957-62 (Box 42, Folder 1131)
  - Cortot, Renée, 1958-62 (Box 42, Folder 1132)
  - Couvreux Ronché, Lucienne
    See: Associazione Italo-Francese di Cultura, Box 33, folder 920
  - Covington and Burling, 1968-85, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1133)
  - Crane, John, 1954-60 (Box 42, Folder 1134)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1966-68
  - Crompton, Yorke, 1952 Jun 10
  - Crosby, Caresse, 1965-69, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1135-37)
  - Cucchetti, Gino, 1970-72, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1138)
  - Cummings, E. E., 1946-48 (Box 42, Folder 1139)
  - Curran, Stuart, 1978-79 (Box 42, Folder 1140)
  - Curtis Brown, Ltd., 1929, 1968
  - Cuthbert, George, n.d.
  - "D" general, 1938-89, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1141-47)
  - Dale, Kathleen, 1924-74, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1148-51)
  - Dalliba-John, Katherine (Ramooth), 1918-36, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1152)
  - Danlienati, Liliana, 1971-82, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1153)
  - Da Nova, Giovanni, 1949, 1950
  - Davenport, Guy, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1154)
  - Davidson, Rosemary, 1982-87, n.d.
  - Dazzi, Manlio Torquato, 1928-72 (Box 43, Folder 1155)
  - De Barbieri Pizzorno, Vittorina, 1964-82 (Box 43, Folder 1156-59)
  - Delaage, Florence, 1960-65, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1160)
  - De Luigi, Janice Cecelia, 1978-80 (Box 43, Folder 1161)
  - Dent, Edward, 1948-50 (Box 43, Folder 1162)
  - De Paoli, Domenico, 1962, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1163)
  - De Picollelis, Elisabetta, 1954-63, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1164)
  - De Scarpis family, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1165)
  - Devlin, Vianney, Rev., 1976-80, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1166)
  - De Wet, Oloff, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 1167)
  - De Zigno, Beatrice, 1949-61 (Box 43, Folder 1168)
  - Diela, Elly, 1945-59, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1169)
  - Dietz, Marc, 1973 Jul 30
  - Di Marzio, Cornelio
    See: Confederatzione Fascista dei Professionisti e degli Artisti, Box 41, folder 1115
  - D'Offay, Anthony, 1974-84 (Box 43, Folder 1170)
  - Dolmetsch, Rudolph, 1939-40 (Box 43, Folder 1171)
  - Donaggio, Irma, 1966-67
  - Dondo, Mrs. Mathurin, 1966 Feb 28
  - Donnelly, Michael, 1980-83 (Box 43, Folder 1172)
  - Doob, Leonard, 1974-75 (Box 43, Folder 1173)
  - Doolittle, Hilda
    See: H. D.
  - Drinker, Sophie, 1938-50 (Box 43, Folder 1174-75)
  - Driver, Clive, 1972 Feb
  - Drummond, Elsie, 1945-57, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1176)
  - Drummond, Fifi, 1948-80, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1177-94)
  - Drummond, John, 1945-70, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1195-1207)
  - Duncan, Ethel, 1934-55, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1208-10)
  - Duncan, Mabel, 1928-46 (Box 44, Folder 1211-13)
  - Duncan, Ronald, 1946-81, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1214-18)
  - Duran, Alex Duran, Vera, 1962-70 (Box 45, Folder 1219)
  - Du Sautoy, Peter, 1965-75, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1220-22)
  - "E" general, 1948-87, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1223-24)
  - Edel, Leon, 1976-87 (Box 45, Folder 1225)
  - Edizioni Scheiwiller
    See: Giovanni (Vanni) Scheiwiller, Box 72, folder 1977
  - Edmunds, John, 1954-55 (Box 45, Folder 1226)
  - Edwards. John, 1954-55, n.d.
  - Einstein, Alfred, 1947-48 (Box 45, Folder 1227)
  - Eliot, Betty, 1959-60, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1228)
  - Eliot, T. S., 1935-55 (Box 45, Folder 1229-32)
  - Eliot, Valerie, 1965-87, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1233-37)
  - Ellmann, Richard, 1971 Sep 19 (Box 46, Folder 1238)
  - Enesco, Georges, 1951-54 (Box 46, Folder 1239)
  - Engel, Ilse, 1970-77 (Box 46, Folder 1240)
  - England, Robert, 1968-73, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1241)
  - Eudre, Otto, 1960-72 (Box 46, Folder 1242)
  - Evans, Illtud, 1959-67, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1243)
  - Evans, Neil, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1244)
  - Everson, William, n.d.
  - "F" general, 1935-88, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1245-48)
  - Faber & Faber, 1949-84, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1249)
    See also: Peter Du Sautoy, Box 45, folder 1220
    See also: T. S. Eliot, Box 45, folder 1229
    See also: Valerie Eliot, Box 45, folder 1233
  - Fagleston, Bill Fagleston, Louie, 1954-58, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1250)
  - Falkner, D. Keith, 1948-49, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1251)
  - Farrell, Patric, 1948-82, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1252)
  - Fasano, Renato, 1958-59 (Box 46, Folder 1253)
  - Fasolo, Ugo, 1967-70
  - Favai, Gennaro, 1930-54 (Box 46, Folder 1254)
  - Favai, Maria, 1945-64, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1255-57)
  - Favaretto, Betty Favaretto, Giorgio, 1952-59 (Box 46, Folder 1258)
  - Federazione Italiana Donne Arti Professioni Affari, 1947-48 (Box 46, Folder 1259)
  - Festival dei Due Mondi, 1973, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1260)
    See also: Gian Carlo Menotti, Box 58, folder 1569
    See also: Vincent Tortora, Box 80, folder 2163
    See also: William Wright, Box 82, folder 2222
  - Filippi, Pauline, 1915 (Box 46, Folder 1261)
  - Fisher, Margaret, 1981-87 (Box 46, Folder 1262)
  - Fitzgerald, Joan, 1963-68 (Box 46, Folder 1263-66)
  - FItzgerald, Joan, 1969-83, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1267-71)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert Fitzgerald, Sally, 1953-70 (Box 47, Folder 1272)
  - Flory, Wendy Stallard, 1980-88, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1273)
  - Flury Nencini, Bianca, 1953-56 (Box 47, Folder 1274)
  - Fondazione Giorgio Cini, 1982-87, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1275)
  - Foote, Edward J., 1972-84 (Box 47, Folder 1276)
  - Foyer, 1951-52 (Box 47, Folder 1277)
  - Franchetti, Luigi, 1937-61, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1278)
  - [Franchetti?], Mimy, 1923, n.d.
  - Franck, Arthur
    See: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3700
  - Frazzi, Vito, 1938-51 (Box 47, Folder 1279)
  - Freedman, Lewis, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1280)
  - Frenberg, Gretta, 1938 Mar 14 (Box 47, Folder 1281)
  - Frost, Ruth Sterling, 1938-49 (Box 47, Folder 1282)
  - Frumi, Lotte, 1984-81, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1283-85)
  - Fujita, F., 1962-63 (Box 47, Folder 1286)
  - Fuller, Buckminister, 1970-75, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1287-88)
  - "G" general, 1937-89, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1289-92)
  - Gabrielli, Liana, 1951-68, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1293-96)
  - Gallup, Donald, 1957-81, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1297-98)
  - Gardner, Elizabeth, 1972-73 (Box 48, Folder 1299)
  - Garegnani, Pierangelo, 1985
  - Gasparetto, Atte, 1955-60 (Box 48, Folder 1300-01)
  - Gavoty, Bernard, 1961-63 (Box 48, Folder 1302)
  - Gay, Harriet, 1976-88, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1303-05)
  - Gerelli, Ennio, 1952-62, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1306-07)
  - Gerlin, Ruggero, 1951-61 (Box 48, Folder 1308)
  - Giles, Hugh, 1952, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1309)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1310)
  - Giuseppe, F., 1959-64 (Box 48, Folder 1311)
  - Gleason, Herbert P.
    See: Hill & Barlow, Box 50, folder 1357
  - Glob, G., 1954-56, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1312-13)
  - Glover, Etta, 1931-38 (Box 48, Folder 1314)
  - Glover, Halcott, 1919-26, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1315)
  - Goldsborough, Arnold Goldsborough, Jocelyn, 1959-62, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1316)
  - Gordon, David, 1976, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 1317)
  - Granchi, Martha, 1958-61
  - Graziani, Mary, 1941-72, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1318-19)
  - Green, Gretchen, 1934 Jul 23 (Box 48, Folder 1320)
  - Green, Martha, 1961, n.d.
  - Grey, Egerton Charles, 1916-28, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1321-25)
  - Grey, Madeleine, 1953 Nov 7 (Box 49, Folder 1326)
  - Grindea, Miron, 1961-81, n.d.
  - Gröen, Niels, 1952-62, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1327-30)
  - Grove's Dictionary of Music and Musicians, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 1331)
  - Guthrie, John, 1963-72, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1332)
  - "H" general, 1915-86, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1333-37)
  - H. D., 1932-61 (Box 49, Folder 1338)
  - Hamblin, Dora Jane (Dodie), 1959-86, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1339-41)
  - Hammond family, 1928-74 (Box 49, Folder 1342)
  - Hargrave, John, 1973 Dec 2 (Box 50, Folder 1343)
  - Harte, Anna Bret, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1344)
  - Harte, Geoffrey Bret, 1920 Jun4
  - Heacock, Esther, 1956-64, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1345-46)
  - Heacock, Priscilla, 1957-66, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1347)
  - Hefferman, Tom, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1348)
  - Hemingway, Ernest (photocopy), 1950 Mar 3 (Box 50, Folder 1349)
  - Hemingway, Mary, 1978, n.d.
  - Henraux s.p.a., 1973-75 (Box 50, Folder 1350)
  - L'Herne
    See: Dominique de Roux, Box 70, folder 1920
  - Hesse, Eva, 1962-72, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1351-54)
  - Hickey, Bernard, 1970-85, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1355-56)
  - Hill & Barlow, 1963-67 (Box 50, Folder 1357)
  - Hohenacker, Harald, 1967-78, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1358)
  - Höhs, Liselotte, 1966-74, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1359-61)
  - Holmquest, Barbara, 1962 Sep 25 (Box 50, Folder 1362)
  - Horton, T. David, 1951 Feb 17
  - Hudson Review, 1950, 1970
  - Hughes, Bob, 1972-80, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1363)
    See also: Margaret Fisher, Box 46, folder 1262
  - Hussey, Dyneley Hussey, Kathleen, 1953, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1364)
  - Hutchins, Patricia, 1964-69, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1365)
  - Hutchison, Kitty, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1366)
  - Huxley, Maria, n.d.
  - "I" general, 1947-83, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1367)
  - Inyoka, Nyota, 1948-58 (Box 50, Folder 1368)
  - Ivancich, Gianfranco, 1965-67, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1369-70)
  - Ivancich Reyes, Emma, 1937-66, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1371-73)
  - "J" general, 1948-89, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1374)
  - Jerdain, Charles, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1375)
  - Jolly, Cynthia, 1950-54
  - Johnson, John Alexander, 1931
  - Jordan, Viola Baxter, 1946-63, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1376-79)
  - Junaut, Marion, 1956-65 (Box 51, Folder 1380)
  - "K" general, 1938-87, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1381-83)
  - Kasper, John, 1951-62, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1384)
  - Kaufman, Annette Kaufman, Louis, 1950-53 (Box 51, Folder 1385-86)
  - Kavka, Jerome, Dr., 1969 Jul 6 (Box 51, Folder 1387)
  - Kean, Katherine, 1971-75
  - Keefe, Helen, 1959-62
  - Kelsey, Joan, 1955-56, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1388)
  - Kenner, Hugh, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1389)
  - Kettle's Yard Gallery, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 1390)
  - Key-Pluymert, Madeleine, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1391)
  - Kilias, Kitsa Kilias, Pantelis, 1957-63 (Box 51, Folder 1392)
  - King, Gibner, 1949-63, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1393-94)
  - Klein, Arthur
    See: Spoken Arts, Inc., Box 79, folder 2114
  - Knocker, E. H., 1937, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1395)
  - Kokoschka, Olda, [1963 Dec]
  - Koster, Dyck, 1952-54 (Box 51, Folder 1396)
  - Krentz, William, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 1397)
  - Kumashiro, Makiko, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1398)
  - Kynaston, Caecelia, 1954-67, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1399-1400)
  - Kynaston, Nicholas, 1957-60, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1401)
  - "L" general, 1936-87, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1402-07)
  - Labia, Maria, 1950, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1408)
  - Lacerda, Alberto de, 1972-73
  - Landschoff, Ludwig, 1938, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 1409)
  - Lansberg, Dorothea M. Watts, 1931-72, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1410)
  - Lanux, Eyre de, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1411)
  - Laughlin, James, 1938-69 (Box 52, Folder 1412-33)
  - Laughlin, James, 1970-88, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1434-42)